(Leonard:)What are you talking about?
SHELDON: Ahem.
PENNY: Oh.
(Sheldon:)Einstein.
Yeah. I'm gonna need a little more.
(Sheldon:)Albert Einstein.
(Leonard:)Keep going.
When Einstein came up
with special relativity...
(Sheldon:)...he was working
at the patent office.
So you're gonna go work
at the patent office?
Oh, don't be absurd.
That's in Washington.
(Sheldon:)I could never live in a city
whose streets are laid out...
(Sheldon:)...in a wheel-and-spoke pattern.
(Sheldon:)No. I'm going to find
a similarly menial job...
(Sheldon:)...where my basal ganglia are occupied
with a routine task...
(Sheldon:)...freeing my prefrontal cortex
to work quietly in the background.
(Leonard:)A great plan.
Of course. Even talking to you
is sufficiently menial.
(Sheldon:)I can feel the proverbial juices
starting to flow.
(Raj:)Okay.
Well, thanks for sharing with us.
(Leonard:)-Good night.
-You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)Good night to you too.
[PENNY & LEONARD SIGH]